<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Understanding Myself]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Understanding Myself]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/understanding-myself/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 18:42:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/understanding-myself/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impulse and fear]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Impulse and fear</h1><p>I struggle a lot with controlling my impulses. And I often
end up doing things that seem really stupid or unnecessary when I look back on
it. I buy stuff I don’t need, eat tons of unhealthy food, waste hours browsing
news sites, YouTube, or other sites filled with brainless entertainment. And I
very often end up avoiding the things I had planned to do if I feel that they
are too hard. And I have been trying hard lately to understand why I behave this
way. I have even gone to see a shrink a few time, in order to find some logic
to what is going on in my head.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/understanding-myself/cd303f18-3953-4ec2-a34b-61825d19da88/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cd303f18-3953-4ec2-a34b-61825d19da88</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 18:42:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feeling Invisible]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Feeling Invisible</h1><p>Right now, it’s Christmas. And both yesterday and today I
spent time with various family. I have noticed or rather I realized one thing
that I have sort of realized before too. When I spend time with all these
people, I feel invisible. It feels like we all get together and talk about
“nothing”. And no one takes any kind of interest in the things I do. Whenever I
interact with anyone, be it with family or work colleagues, it’s never about
me. And it becomes very difficult to share when there is so little interest the
times I try to. It feels as if the more I try to interact with others, the more
invisible I become.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/understanding-myself/feeling-invisible/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cdc2d60e-5c1a-41f2-a975-426597df16f2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 18:41:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Addiction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Addiction</h1><p>I struggle with a few addictions. One has to do with the
fact that I can never do anything partly. So if I start, for example, to watch
something, I feel the need to watch and buy anything related to it. And that
can be a pretty big problem when I watch, read or play many things. And some of
these things are part of major franchises that includes content in all kinds of
mediums, that both costs a lot of money to get and takes a lot of time to just
find in the first place if it includes out of print products and such. The
truth is that it just isn’t fun at all. But jet I keep looking for new stuff to
collect. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/understanding-myself/addiction/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9c31cdf6-fab6-4292-bdc8-c354bb99299c</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 18:40:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is money?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>What is money?</h1><p>What is money? We all use money, but we rarely actually
think about what money really is. The easiest way to realize what it is to start
by looking at a basic society without money. If you have a small group of
people living together in an isolated community. Then everyone helps each other
and everyone receives the things they need to survive.People help out not because they want to gain
something, but because they want to feel like a useful part of the group.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/understanding-myself/what-is-money/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b0cb0eaa-7152-43ca-936c-d03ee3a9dfa6</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 18:39:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does A have to lead to B?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Does A have to lead to B?</h1><p>We usually tend to do things in sequence or order. I do one
thing so therefore I do another thing. It’s a useful way of doing things when
it comes to improving our skills and abilities in life. I learn one thing then
another thing that builds upon the first thing and eventually learn to master
something very complicated and useful. But when we are faced with so many
things we can do, like we are in today’s world, this way of doing things can
also cause a lot of trouble for us. I watch a movie that I enjoy and therefore
I have to see all its sequels as well. I buy a book that I like and therefore I
need to buy all the books written by that author. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/understanding-myself/does-a-have-to-lead-to-b/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a8ea74e6-925b-4d82-950c-e031562ae853</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 18:35:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Willpower]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Willpower</h1><p>What is willpower and how can I get better at using it? I
have been thinking a lot about these kinds of questions lately. One answer I
have reached, is that willpower is probably best defined as the ability to
resist my natural instincts. When I give into impulses for instance, it is
because my natural instincts tell me I should do it. What I mean by this is,
when I get an idea or some kind of urge, what often happens is that I go into a
kind of panic mode. My brain is telling me that this thing, whatever it is, is
so important that I just have to get it “now!”. So essentially I get so scared
of not giving into the impulse that I end up giving into it. What this means
then is that my lack of impulse control has to do with me having a lack of
courage.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/understanding-myself/willpower/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">59069bf4-373c-44cb-b195-7ea2e90dac08</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 18:34:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who am I]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Who am I</h1><p>I thought I would start this blog by writing a bit about
myself and why I decided to start this blog. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/understanding-myself/who-am-i/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">afe2631e-4fbb-42a2-9852-475f12c350b8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 18:18:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>